[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "Which of the following is true regarding learning in psychology?",
    "options": [
      "Learning has not been an important topic in psychology",
      "Learning involves no change in the organism",
      "Learning focuses on how humans speak",
      "Learning can be defined in many ways"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "Learning is seen as an effect attributed to an element in",
    "options": [
      "blood",
      "environment",
      "hormones",
      "none of the above"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "Non-associative learning refers to __________ in the intensity of a response as the result of the repeated presentation of a stimulus.",
    "options": [
      "a decrease",
      "an increase",
      "no change",
      "none of the above"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "Which of the following is a type of learning style?",
    "options": [
      "visual",
      "auditory",
      "kinesthetic",
      "all of the above"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "'Psychology as the Behaviorist Views It' is the famous work of",
    "options": [
      "Sigmund Freud",
      "John Watson",
      "Albert Bandura",
      "Ivan Pavlov"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "The state of conscious incompetence may be valuable __________ of a learning experience.",
    "options": [
      "at the start",
      "at the end",
      "in the middle",
      "throughout the process"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "Adding to existing student knowledge is known as",
    "options": [
      "conceptual change",
      "conceptual pattern",
      "conceptual exploration",
      "conceptual growth"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "Deliberate practice involves the following, except",
    "options": [
      "attention",
      "rehearsal",
      "repetition",
      "forgetting"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "Students persist in the face of challenging tasks and process information more deeply when they adopt __________ goals.",
    "options": [
      "performance",
      "insignificant",
      "mastery",
      "repetitive"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "__________ refers to a decrease in response rate while __________ refers to an increase in response rate.",
    "options": [
      "sensitization, habituation.",
      "meaningful learning, association",
      "habituation, sensitization",
      "association, meaningful learning"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 2
  }
]